myhpf.co.uk 2009-01-30

# homepages friends - signup

## The Homepages Friends Privacy Policy

### What Information Is Collected:

Homepages Friends collect personal information when you register as a customer with Homepages Friends, through product enquiry and registration forms and when you email your details. Homepages Friends also collect information about visitors to the web site. This includes details of what was visited and when, where visitors come from and the type of software used. None of this data includes any information that would allow you or any other person to be identified.

### How Homepages Friends Use This Information:

If you are a customer of HomePages Friends, Homepages Friends may use your personal information to:

\- To check that you are a valid customer if you contact Homepages Friends for support.

\- To assist in identifying you, you may be asked for personal details submitted as part of any registration process.

\- Your contact details will also be used to communicate with you. Homepages Friends may use your information to send you offers and news about Homepages Friends products and services. Homepages Friends may contact you by post, email, telephone or fax for these purposes.

\- Collect payment from you for Homepages Friends provided services

\- Homepages Friends will not disclose any personal information we keep about you or any other customers to any third parties.

Should there be any change to the Homepages Friends privacy policy we will inform you of the changes via this page, and where the changes apply to the holding of or sharing of personal data we will obtain your permission to do this.

### National Security & Crime Prevention:

Homepages Friends may be required to divulge certain details of users to national security and crime prevention agencies. Such information will only be divulged in accordance with the requirements of relevant legislation and on properly actioned and authenticated requests. Homepages Friends may be required to retain certain items of personal information in order to comply with legislation.

### Third Party Sites:

Our privacy policy does not apply to third party sites that you may access from our website. We recommend that you check the privacy policies of those sites before entering any personal data into third party sites and pages.

### Consent:

By disclosing your personal information to Homepages Friends, if you have already registered, by continuing as a customer of Homepages Friends , you give your consent to the collection, storage, processing and use of your personal information by us as described in this policy.
